firstquarterfinance.com 2019-08-06

# Privacy Policy: FQF's Outline of How We Collect Information & Your Rights

This policy is applicable to firstquarterfinance.com and its associated pages. We reserve the right to change and update this policy at any time. It is your responsibility to be aware of any changes. You may also like to review our [Terms of Use](https://firstquarterfinance.com/terms-of-use/).

Note that links contained on First Quarter Finance pages may bring you to third-party websites. These sites are not maintained by First Quarter Finance; we retain no liability for the content and policies on those websites. When following a link to a third party, you may want to review its Privacy Policy and Terms of Use before using that website.

## Does First Quarter Finance collect information about me?

Yes, First Quarter Finance collects some visitor data via cookies. The information we collect helps us understand the interests of users and improve our website to optimize your experience.

Cookies are primarily used to help us display ads that are relevant to you, such as a discount on your favorite brand of running shoes or a charity you may like to support.

Cookies do not store any personal information, nor can they introduce a virus to your computer. This is unlike spyware, which sends information about your browsing history across the internet to a third party. First Quarter Finance does not use spyware.

First Quarter Finance does not sell, give, or trade the statistics we store to any third parties for the purposes of data mining, marketing, or any other reason.

We do not use browser popups, including push notifications.

Most browsers allow you to accept and/or delete cookies.

## How do I block cookies?

Please note that blocking cookies may have a negative impact on the functions of a website. Some features may cease to be available. Depending on the browser you use, you can set your preferences to block/refuse cookies and/or notify you before they are used. Here’s how to block cookies on each of the most common browsers:

## What does First Quarter Finance do with the information I volunteer?

When you interact with the site by either a contact page or a comment, you must provide your name and email address. Names and email addresses are not publicly displayed unless you’re leaving a comment — and then, only your name is displayed. You will be made aware of this before submitting your comment.

First Quarter Finance does not sell, give, or trade the statistics we receive to any third parties for the purposes of data mining, marketing, or any other reason.

If you’re a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have additional rights to:

  * Access your personal data
  * Ensure the accuracy of your personal data
  * Have us delete your personal data
  * Require us to stop gathering your personal data
  * Bring issues up with a supervisory authority if any data is being improperly used

## How often is this Privacy Policy updated?

We update this policy about every quarter. By using our site, you consent to our current policy.

## How can I contact First Quarter Finance with questions/comments/concerns about my privacy?

We take your privacy very seriously. Please send us a message through [our Contact Us page](https://firstquarterfinance.com/contact-us/) or send mail to:

 **More Holdings LLC**  
7400 Tallgrass Parkway, 307A  
Lincoln, NE 68521

 _Updated 08/06/19_
